{
    "id": "18758a80f7854f149df8e6f68e10b017",
    "title": "Gap Fills",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I want to know why …………………. late.",
            "description": "In indirect questions, the subject goes before the auxiliary verb.",
            "answers": [
                "are you",
                "you are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3052fe0fd3e947b49d8bf2965ee8367f"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you had asked me I …………………… you.",
            "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if-clause and would have + past participle in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "would tell",
                "will tell",
                "would have told"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cd40e932364b4ff59f1200e5a87cb7e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "She would have come if you ………………………. her.",
            "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if-clause and would have + past participle in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "invited",
                "invites",
                "had invited"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9b839b060f434df0bca0bb83f304750b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The more you praise him, ……………………. he becomes.",
            "description": "In this structure, we need the + comparative in both clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "worse",
                "the worse",
                "the worst"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4566fd083a6947f182a72008c19e1138"
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner had the teacher entered the class …………………….. the students stood up.",
            "description": "Sooner is a comparative word use than after it. ",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "when",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e8f4ff9c52b3427d97caf0d46f64b3d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind …………………….. me your book?",
            "description": "The ing form is used after do you mind and would you mind.",
            "answers": [
                "lending",
                "to lend",
                "lend"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "413ce4e6c2df458ca2724cf34f795ede"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is too lazy …………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to work",
                "to working",
                "for work"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "db11224aefd9470bb8b80367cf26ee1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He enjoys ……………………. with children.",
            "description": "Enjoy cannot be followed by a to-infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "playing",
                "to play",
                "to playing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "015e2636b0674f78b80b794768b1c501"
        },
        {
            "question": "He accused me …………………… stealing his watch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ea414b50a5e8488d858df755f75e1975"
        },
        {
            "question": "He congratulated me ……………………… my success.",
            "description": "Both for and on can be used.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "76064543b27f423dbd0c95997cac541a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was acquitted …………………… the charges levelled against him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "of",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bb68dc434ec24f1c88a7dc577f404e6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. the bell rang, the students rushed to the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No sooner",
                "Hardly",
                "As soon as"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a69fc690a59d4a12a80543209a0cf526"
        }
    ]
}